[
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "clubs", "spades"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"king", "10", "7"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "spades", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"ace", "king", "10"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_diamonds",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "hearts", "spades"
			],
			"answer": "diamonds"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"10", "jack", "king"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "hearts", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"queen", "8", "jack"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "spades", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"7", "8", "queen"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "diamonds", "clubs"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"8", "7", "jack"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "clubs", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"ace", "8", "7"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "spades", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"queen", "8", "9"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"spades", "hearts", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"queen", "8", "king"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "spades", "clubs"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"jack", "king", "8"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "clubs", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"king", "8", "10"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "spades", "clubs"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"10", "9", "jack"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"spades", "diamonds", "clubs"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"queen", "7", "ace"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_diamonds",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "hearts", "spades"
			],
			"answer": "diamonds"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"jack", "queen", "10"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_diamonds",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"spades", "hearts", "clubs"
			],
			"answer": "diamonds"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"8", "6", "ace"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"spades", "diamonds", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "jack", "ace"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "clubs", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"7", "ace", "jack"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "clubs", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"jack", "6", "9"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_diamonds",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "spades", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "diamonds"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "7", "jack"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "diamonds", "spades"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"king", "10", "ace"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "spades", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"10", "queen", "ace"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "hearts", "spades"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"7", "10", "8"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "spades", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"ace", "9", "jack"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_6_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "spades", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"10", "jack", "queen"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "spades", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "6", "queen"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "hearts", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"6", "9", "10"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "clubs", "spades"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "queen", "ace"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_king_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "clubs", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"10", "7", "9"
			],
			"answer": "king"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_diamonds",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"hearts", "spades", "clubs"
			],
			"answer": "diamonds"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"6", "9", "king"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_diamonds",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "spades", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "diamonds"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"queen", "7", "king"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_spades",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "diamonds", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "spades"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "ace", "6"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "diamonds", "spades"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "queen", "ace"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"spades", "diamonds", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "ace", "king"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_clubs",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"diamonds", "spades", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "clubs"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "queen", "10"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_hearts",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"clubs", "spades", "diamonds"
			],
			"answer": "hearts"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"10", "7", "9"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "playing card",
		"filename": "card_8_diamonds",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 4,
		"conflict": "playing card",
		"questions": [{
			"question": "What suit was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"spades", "clubs", "hearts"
			],
			"answer": "diamonds"
		},
		{
			"question": "What card was the %?",
			"distractors": [
				"9", "6", "jack"
			],
			"answer": "8"
		}
	]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_1",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"9","2","4"
				],
				"answer":"1"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"purple","green","brown"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"stripe"
				],
				"answer":"solid"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_2",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"3","11","7"
				],
				"answer":"2"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"orange","yellow","brown"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"stripe"
				],
				"answer":"solid"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_7",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"8","14","15"
				],
				"answer":"7"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","blue","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"brown"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"stripe"
				],
				"answer":"solid"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_5",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"11","6","7"
				],
				"answer":"5"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"black","green","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"orange"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"stripe"
				],
				"answer":"solid"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_12",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"11","13","14"
				],
				"answer":"12"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"black","red","orange"
				],
				"answer":"purple"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_6",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"11","5","12"
				],
				"answer":"6"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"orange","yellow","brown"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"stripe"
				],
				"answer":"solid"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_14",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"15","5","2"
				],
				"answer":"14"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","brown","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_10",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"13","15","1"
				],
				"answer":"10"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"purple","brown","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_5",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"7","10","11"
				],
				"answer":"5"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","black","purple"
				],
				"answer":"orange"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"stripe"
				],
				"answer":"solid"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_12",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"7","3","2"
				],
				"answer":"12"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"black","green","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"purple"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_11",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"13","8","6"
				],
				"answer":"11"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"purple","orange","blue"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_10",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"7","15","1"
				],
				"answer":"10"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"brown","yellow","red"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_13",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"5","1","15"
				],
				"answer":"13"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","black","purple"
				],
				"answer":"orange"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_14",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"2","10","11"
				],
				"answer":"14"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","black","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_15",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"12","10","11"
				],
				"answer":"15"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","black","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"brown"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"solid"
				],
				"answer":"stripe"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "billiard ball",
		"filename": "billiardball_4",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"billiard ball",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"6","5","9"
				],
				"answer":"4"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"orange","blue","red"
				],
				"answer":"purple"
			},
			{
				"question":"What pattern was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"stripe"
				],
				"answer":"solid"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_1",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"8","3","5"
				],
				"answer":"1"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","red","green"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_2",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"1","9","3"
				],
				"answer":"2"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","red","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_3",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"6","5","2"
				],
				"answer":"3"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","green","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_4",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"1","2","6"
				],
				"answer":"4"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"yellow","blue","red"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_5",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"3","8","7"
				],
				"answer":"5"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","red","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_6",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"1","8","4"
				],
				"answer":"6"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","yellow","red"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_7",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"6","3","1"
				],
				"answer":"7"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","red","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_8",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"2","3","7"
				],
				"answer":"8"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","red","green"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_9",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What number was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"5","6","8"
				],
				"answer":"9"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","green","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_A",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"W","Z","O"
				],
				"answer":"A"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","yellow","green"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_B",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"P","T","Q"
				],
				"answer":"B"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"yellow","green","red"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_C",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"U","G","L"
				],
				"answer":"C"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","blue","green"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_D",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"K","N","B"
				],
				"answer":"D"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","yellow","green"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_E",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"A","F","Z"
				],
				"answer":"E"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","green","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_F",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"A","O","Y"
				],
				"answer":"F"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","yellow","red"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_G",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"O","F","T"
				],
				"answer":"G"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","blue","green"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_H",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"S","Y","U"
				],
				"answer":"H"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"yellow","green","red"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_I",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"O","F","R"
				],
				"answer":"I"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","yellow","blue"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_J",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"L","R","Y"
				],
				"answer":"J"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","red","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_K",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"M","G","D"
				],
				"answer":"K"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","red","blue"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_L",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"E","F","W"
				],
				"answer":"L"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","yellow","green"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_M",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"V","P","H"
				],
				"answer":"M"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","yellow","blue"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_N",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"K","V","Y"
				],
				"answer":"N"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","yellow","red"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_O",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"H","E","C"
				],
				"answer":"O"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","green","blue"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_P",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Y","X","W"
				],
				"answer":"P"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","red","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_Q",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"P","H","I"
				],
				"answer":"Q"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","blue","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_R",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"E","B","L"
				],
				"answer":"R"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","red","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_S",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"J","T","H"
				],
				"answer":"S"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","blue","red"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_T",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Y","F","V"
				],
				"answer":"T"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","yellow","green"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_U",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"S","L","O"
				],
				"answer":"U"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"yellow","blue","green"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_V",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"M","B","J"
				],
				"answer":"V"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"yellow","blue","red"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_W",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"D","R","O"
				],
				"answer":"W"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","red","blue"
				],
				"answer":"yellow"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_X",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"W","Q","I"
				],
				"answer":"X"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","yellow","green"
				],
				"answer":"blue"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_Y",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"F","X","W"
				],
				"answer":"Y"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"blue","green","yellow"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "block",
		"filename": "block_letter_Z",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"block",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What letter was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Y","A","M"
				],
				"answer":"Z"
			},
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"yellow","blue","red"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "dice",
		"filename": "dice_single_green_1",
		"x": 1,
		"y": 1,
		"conflict":"dice",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"red","white","blue"
				],
				"answer":"green"
			},
			{
				"question":"What number was showing on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					2,4,5
				],
				"answer":1
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "dice",
		"filename": "dice_single_red_2",
		"x": 1,
		"y": 1,
		"conflict":"dice",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","white","blue"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			},
			{
				"question":"What number was showing on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					1,4,5
				],
				"answer":2
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "dice",
		"filename": "dice_single_white_4",
		"x": 1,
		"y": 1,
		"conflict":"dice",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What color was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","red","blue"
				],
				"answer":"white"
			},
			{
				"question":"What number was showing on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					1,2,5
				],
				"answer":4
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "dice",
		"filename": "dice_4",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"dice",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"How many % were there?",
				"distractors":[
					3,5,2
				],
				"answer":4
			},
			{
				"question":"How many red % were there?",
				"distractors":[
					1,0,3
				],
				"answer":2
			},
			{
				"question":"How many green % were there?",
				"distractors":[
					2,0,3
				],
				"answer":1
			},
			{
				"question":"How many white % were there?",
				"distractors":[
					2,0,3
				],
				"answer":1
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the total of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					10,8,9
				],
				"answer":11
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "clock",
		"filename": "clock_red_130",
		"x": 3,
		"y": 3,
		"conflict":"clock",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"What color was the border of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"green","black","blue"
				],
				"answer":"red"
			},
			{
				"question":"What time was showing on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"2:30","3:30","2:00"
				],
				"answer":"1:30"
			},
			{
				"question":"Where was the second-hand on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Between 1 & 2","Between 10 & 11","Between 9 & 10"
				],
				"answer":"Between 11 & 12"
			},
			{
				"question":"What shape were the hour markers on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Diamonds", "Dashes","Squares"
				],
				"answer":"Circles"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_dime_heads",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"tails"
				],
				"answer":"heads"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"nickel","quarter","penny"
				],
				"answer":"dime"
			},
			{
				"question":"What year was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"2013","2015","2005"
				],
				"answer":"2003"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the bottom of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"In God We Trust"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the left side of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"In God We Trust", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"Liberty"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_dime_tails",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"heads"
				],
				"answer":"tails"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"nickel","quarter","penny"
				],
				"answer":"dime"
			},
			{
				"question":"What image is shown on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"a building","a President","an eagle"
				],
				"answer":"a torch"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the top of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","In God We Trust"
				],
				"answer":"United States of America"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_nickel_heads",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"tails"
				],
				"answer":"heads"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"dime","quarter","penny"
				],
				"answer":"nickel"
			},
			{
				"question":"What year was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"1985","2015","2005"
				],
				"answer":"1995"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the left side of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"In God We Trust"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the right side of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"In God We Trust", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"Liberty"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_nickel_tails",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"heads"
				],
				"answer":"tails"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"dime","quarter","penny"
				],
				"answer":"nickel"
			},
			{
				"question":"What image is shown on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"a torch","a President","an eagle"
				],
				"answer":"a building"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the top of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "United States of America","In God We Trust"
				],
				"answer":"E Pluribus Unum"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the bottom of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","In God We Trust"
				],
				"answer":"United States of America"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_penny_heads",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"tails"
				],
				"answer":"heads"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"dime","quarter","nickel"
				],
				"answer":"penny"
			},
			{
				"question":"What year was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"2005","2016","2015"
				],
				"answer":"2006"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the left side of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"In God We Trust", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"Liberty"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the top of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"In God We Trust"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_penny_tails",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"heads"
				],
				"answer":"tails"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"dime","quarter","nickel"
				],
				"answer":"penny"
			},
			{
				"question":"What image is shown on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"a torch","a President","an eagle"
				],
				"answer":"a building"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the top of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","In God We Trust"
				],
				"answer":"United States of America"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_quarter_heads",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"tails"
				],
				"answer":"heads"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"dime","penny","nickel"
				],
				"answer":"quarter"
			},
			{
				"question":"What year was the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"1988","1994","1998"
				],
				"answer":"1984"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the top of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"In God We Trust", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"Liberty"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the left side of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","United States of America"
				],
				"answer":"In God We Trust"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"name": "coin",
		"filename": "coin_quarter_tails",
		"x": 2,
		"y": 2,
		"conflict":"coin",
		"questions":[
			{
				"question":"Which side was facing up on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"heads"
				],
				"answer":"tails"
			},
			{
				"question":"What was the denomination of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"dime","penny","nickel"
				],
				"answer":"quarter"
			},
			{
				"question":"What image is shown on the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"a torch","a President","a building"
				],
				"answer":"an eagle"
			},
			{
				"question":"What is written on the top of the %?",
				"distractors":[
					"Liberty", "E Pluribus Unum","In God We Trust"
				],
				"answer":"United States of America"
			}
		]
	},
	{
					"name": "button",
					"filename": "button_blue",
					"x": 2,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"button",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"How many holes were in the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"4"
						],
						"answer":"2"
					},
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"brown","orange","green"
						],
						"answer":"blue"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "button",
					"filename": "button_brown",
					"x": 2,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"button",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"How many holes were in the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"2"
						],
						"answer":"4"
					},
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","orange","yellow"
						],
						"answer":"brown"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "button",
					"filename": "button_green",
					"x": 2,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"button",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"How many holes were in the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"4"
						],
						"answer":"2"
					},
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"brown","yellow","blue"
						],
						"answer":"green"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "button",
					"filename": "button_orange",
					"x": 2,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"button",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"How many holes were in the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"4"
						],
						"answer":"2"
					},
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","red","yellow"
						],
						"answer":"orange"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "button",
					"filename": "button_yellow",
					"x": 2,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"button",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"How many holes were in the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"2"
						],
						"answer":"4"
					},
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"red","black","orange"
						],
						"answer":"yellow"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "button",
				"filename": "button_black",
				"x": 2,
				"y": 2,
				"conflict":"button",
				"questions":[
				{
					"question":"How many holes were in the %?",
					"distractors":[
						"2"
					],
					"answer":"4"
				},
				{
					"question":"What color was the %?",
					"distractors":[
						"red","brown","blue"
					],
					"answer":"black"
				}
			]
		},
		{
				"name": "poker chip",
				"filename": "poker_chip_black",
				"x": 2,
				"y": 2,
				"conflict":"poker chip",
				"questions":[
				{
					"question":"What color was the %?",
					"distractors":[
						"brown","blue","yellow"
					],
					"answer":"black"
				}
			]
		},
			{
				"name": "poker chip",
				"filename": "poker_chip_blue",
				"x": 2,
				"y": 2,
				"conflict":"poker chip",
				"questions":[
				{
					"question":"What color was the %?",
					"distractors":[
						"yellow","black","orange"
					],
					"answer":"blue"
				}
			]
		},
			{
				"name": "poker chip",
				"filename": "poker_chip_green",
				"x": 2,
				"y": 2,
				"conflict":"poker chip",
				"questions":[
				{
					"question":"What color was the %?",
					"distractors":[
						"brown","red","yellow"
					],
					"answer":"green"
				}
			]
		},
			{
				"name": "poker chip",
				"filename": "poker_chip_red",
				"x": 2,
				"y": 2,
				"conflict":"poker chip",
				"questions":[
				{
					"question":"What color was the %?",
					"distractors":[
						"yellow","blue","brown"
					],
					"answer":"red"
				}
			]
		},
		{
					"name": "paper clip",
					"filename": "paperclip_blue",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"paper clip",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","yellow","red"
						],
						"answer":"blue"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "paper clip",
					"filename": "paperclip_green",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"paper clip",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","blue","yellow"
						],
						"answer":"green"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "paper clip",
					"filename": "paperclip_orange",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"paper clip",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","blue","yellow"
						],
						"answer":"orange"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "paper clip",
					"filename": "paperclip_pink",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"paper clip",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","orange","yellow"
						],
						"answer":"pink"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "paper clip",
					"filename": "paperclip_red",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"paper clip",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","yellow","orange"
						],
						"answer":"red"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "paper clip",
					"filename": "paperclip_yellow",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"paper clip",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","brown","orange"
						],
						"answer":"yellow"
					}
				]
			},
			{
					"name": "tack",
					"filename": "tack_blue",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"tack",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"orange","black","green"
						],
						"answer":"blue"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "tack",
					"filename": "tack_green",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"tack",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","brown","blue"
						],
						"answer":"green"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "tack",
					"filename": "tack_orange",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"tack",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"red","brown","black"
						],
						"answer":"orange"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "tack",
					"filename": "tack_red",
					"x": 1,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"tack",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"yellow","black","blue"
						],
						"answer":"red"
					}
				]
			},
			{
					"name": "crayon",
					"filename": "crayon_blue",
					"x": 4,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"crayon",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"brown","green","yellow"
						],
						"answer":"blue"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "crayon",
					"filename": "crayon_brown",
					"x": 4,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"crayon",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","green","red"
						],
						"answer":"brown"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "crayon",
					"filename": "crayon_green",
					"x": 4,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"crayon",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"yellow","black","red"
						],
						"answer":"green"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "crayon",
					"filename": "crayon_purple",
					"x": 4,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"crayon",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"black","green","orange"
						],
						"answer":"purple"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "crayon",
					"filename": "crayon_red",
					"x": 4,
					"y": 1,
					"conflict":"crayon",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"orange","brown","green"
						],
						"answer":"red"
					}
				]
			},
			{
					"name": "ticket",
					"filename": "ticket_blue",
					"x": 3,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"ticket",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"red","orange","brown"
						],
						"answer":"blue"
					},
					{
						"question":"What number was on the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"4051","6113","4829"
						],
						"answer":"6831"
					}
				]
			},
				{
					"name": "ticket",
					"filename": "ticket_green",
					"x": 3,
					"y": 2,
					"conflict":"ticket",
					"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"orange","red","brown"
						],
						"answer":"green"
					},
					{
						"question":"What number was on the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"6113","4051","4829"
						],
						"answer":"6831"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "ticket",
				"filename": "ticket_red",
				"x": 3,
				"y": 2,
				"conflict":"ticket",
				"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","orange","blue"
						],
						"answer":"red"
					},
					{
						"question":"What number was on the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"4051","6113","4829"
						],
						"answer":"6831"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "pen",
				"filename": "pen_blue",
				"x": 1,
				"y": 6,
				"conflict":"pen",
				"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","black","red"
						],
						"answer":"blue"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "pen",
				"filename": "pen_red",
				"x": 1,
				"y": 6,
				"conflict":"pen",
				"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","black","blue"
						],
						"answer":"red"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "pen",
				"filename": "pen_silver",
				"x": 1,
				"y": 6,
				"conflict":"pen",
				"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","black","red"
						],
						"answer":"silver"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "pen",
				"filename": "pen_yellow_and_blue",
				"x": 1,
				"y": 6,
				"conflict":"pen",
				"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"blue with a yellow cap","red with a black cap","black with a red cap"
						],
						"answer":"yellow with a blue cap"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "pencil",
				"filename": "pencil_yellow",
				"x": 1,
				"y": 6,
				"conflict":"pen",
				"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"green","red","white"
						],
						"answer":"yellow"
					},
					{
						"question":"What color was the %'s eraser?",
						"distractors":[
							"pink","red","green"
						],
						"answer":"white"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"name": "highlighter",
				"filename": "highlighter_orange",
				"x": 1,
				"y": 6,
				"conflict":"pen",
				"questions":[
					{
						"question":"What color was the %?",
						"distractors":[
							"yellow","red","green"
						],
						"answer":"orange"
					}
				]
			}
]